■ krokowski.dx@gmail.com | ★ www.krokowski0x.com | □ krokowski0x | □ krokowski0x

## Summary \_\_\_

I'm a student, with passion for Software Engineering, learning cutting edge technologies and everything related to JavaScript, currently working on multiple personal and team projects, wanting to gain experience, deliver solutions on new challenging tasks and meet inspiring people. I offer full commitment, 12h+/day availability, potential, ability to focus on performed task, high communication and team work skills.

# **Projects**

**Interactive AVL Tree** March 2018

- · Implemented an AVL Tree in vanilla ES6+, based on Object-Oriented Programming principles
- Visualized the tree with semantic HTML5, CSS3 Grid and p5.js, then deployed app to Heroku

**Live Sorting Test** April 2018

- · Programmed an app for testing different sorting alghoritms and comparing their big O execution time
- · Achieved high performance due to real-time, server-side, multi-threaded Node.js computing
- Designed custom Express API and fully mocked it with Web Workers

ShallowBlue.js May 2018

- · Programmed and visualized chess AI using minimax with alfa-beta pruning
- Developed separate branches for Redux and React Context API based application state
- Highly focused on code readability with ESLint, Webpack 4 and Sass
- Currently applying reinforcement learning with deep neural network in Tensorflow.js

CryptoPi.js June 2018

- Developed gesture-controlled, real-time, Web Socket based cryptocurrency price-tracking app
- Controlled hardware with Raspberry Pi/Arduino, GDAX API, JohnnyFive.js and Node.js
- Currently adding Google Assistant voice integration with custom commands

#### **Project Offtop (Team Project)**

March 2018 - Present

- · Designed and mocked big web app, that would be the dashboard of all student's activity at the university
- Created a team of about 40 students, run a series of lectures about Front-End Development
- · Currently creating git issues, holding meetings on scalability & security and further developing API
- Delegated teams for data fetching, backend services and database creation

**Other Notable Projects** 

- · Developed tab sorting Chrome Extension with functional JavaScript for own convenience
- Developed Node.js app checking for air pollution with geolocation and weather APIs
- Developed and fully tested MATLAB/C/C++/8051 Assembly apps being supervised by course tutors

# Work Experience.

### Incognito Cocktail Bar/Kofeina

Wroclaw, Poland

BARTENDER, THEN PR/SOCIAL MEDIA MARKETING MANAGER • Gained strong foundation on how the web and users' attention works Jul. 2016 - Present

- · Learned how to design custom UX, create products tailored to client's needs
- · Worked long hours with a high performing team in fast-paced, high stress environment

#### Manuli Ekobal Sp. z.o.o

Wroclaw, Poland May 2017 - May 2018

SEO Specialist/UI Designer/Site Administration

- Proposed and implemented full redesign of company's website
- Reduced website's payload size by a third, improved page speed rankings, cut load time by 50%
- Boosted monthly traffic from around 5k to above 13k visits/month, organized meetings, met deadlines
- Gained experience working with servers and site maintanance in big, international B2B company

## Education

### **Wroclaw University of Science and Technology**

Wroclaw, Poland

BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING IN CONTROL ENGINEERING AND ROBOTICS

Took courses including Computer Science, Alghoritm Design, Artificial Intelligence and Advanced Calculus & Algebra,

Oct. 2016 - Exp. Jun. 2021